http://www.iaapsy.org/help/privacy-statement/

Meetings & Publications
Applied Psychology Around the World (APAW)
Web Briefings
IAAP is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the IAAP site and governs data collection and usage. By using the IAAP site, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
IAAP collects personally identifiable information, such as your email address, name, home or work address or telephone number. IAAP also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites. For the purposes of GDPR the data controller is the IAAP Operations Center; they can be contacted at operationscenter@iaapsy.org
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by IAAP. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by IAAP for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the IAAP site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through IAAP public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: IAAP does not read any of your private online communications.
IAAP encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from IAAP so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. IAAP is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the IAAP and IAAP family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
IAAP collects and uses your personal information to operate the IAAP Web site and deliver the services you have requested. IAAP also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from IAAP and its affiliates. IAAP may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
IAAP does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. IAAP may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, IAAP may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to IAAP, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
IAAP is an international organization headquartered in the United States of America and as such data we have collected from you is maintained outside of the European Econmic Area (EEA). We comply with the Data Protection Act 1998. By using this website you consent to the storage of your personal data in systems located outside of the European Economic Area (EEA).
IAAP does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
IAAP keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within IAAP, in order to determine what IAAP services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within IAAP to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
IAAP Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on IAAP or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of IAAP; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of IAAP, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The IAAP Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize IAAP pages, or register with IAAP site or services, a cookie helps IAAP to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same IAAP Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the IAAP features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the IAAP services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
IAAP secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. IAAP secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Maintaining and Removing Your Personal Data
If you have a registered account with IAAP, we provide you with tools to access, correct, and modify the personal data you provided to us.
To request that your data be removed entirely from IAAP's database, please contact operationscenter@iaapsy.org
Changes to this Statement
IAAP will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. IAAP encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how IAAP is protecting your information.
Contact Information
IAAP welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that IAAP has not adhered to this Statement, please contact IAAP at operationscenter@iaapsy.org. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Copyright 2020 IAAP
Privacy Statement
|
Terms of Use
About IAAP
Governance & Structure
Board
Committees
Applied Psychology Around the World (APAW)
